mdundo.com 2019-03-30

# Privacy policy | Mdundo.com

This privacy policy sets out how Mdundo.com uses and protects any information that you give Mdundo.com when you use this website. 

Mdundo.com is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. 

Mdundo.com may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 27.03.2014 

### Content Provider Account

Access to certain Services is only available to registered users; specifically, Content Uploaders. 

When you register to use this Platform as a Content Uploader, you will provide us with your email address, and will choose a username and password for your account. You must ensure that the email address that you provide is, and remains, valid for Mdundo to be able to keep you updated with any changes made on the Privacy Policy as well as Terms and Conditions and to share any promotional news and items. Your email address and any other information you choose to provide about yourself will be treated in accordance with our Privacy Policy. 

Customer Users shall be bound by the Customer Terms and Conditions. (Insert link) ... http://mdundo.com/terms

**a) Password**

The Content Uploader is solely responsible for maintaining the confidentiality and security of your username and password, and will remain responsible for all use of their username and password, and all activity emanating from your account, whether or not such activity was authorized by you. 

If the username or password is lost or stolen, or if you believe that unauthorized third parties have accessed the account, the Content Uploader is advised to notify Mdundo in writing through artist@mdundo.com , and should change your password at the earliest possible opportunity. 

**b) Content to be deleted on cancellation of your account**

Any attempt to terminate a Content Uploader’s account by means other than those described in the Termination section will not be considered a proper termination. 

Once your account has been terminated, any and all Content residing in your account, or pertaining to activity from your account (for example, data relating to the distribution or consumption of your sounds), will be irretrievably deleted by Mdundo, except to the extent that we are obliged or permitted to retain such content, data or information for a certain period of time in accordance with applicable laws and regulations and/or to protect our legitimate business interests. Mdundo shall not provide you with any file of data relating to activity associated with your account, whether before or after termination. This data is provided and is accessible only for viewing via your account page on the Website for as long as your account is active. 

### Customer User Account

Mdundo collect the following information: - Your name - Your location - Your phone number 

Mdundo requires this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons: -   
Let our artists, our partners or other third parties contact you.   
Internal record keeping. -  
Keep you posted on any changes in the Privacy Policy and promotional campaigns for your benefit.  
We may use the information to improve our products and services, customise the website according to your interests. 

### Security 

Mdundo is committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, Mdundo has put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.   

### Cookies

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences. 

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes. 

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. 

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
